https://allincu.com/privacy-policy.html

Skip to Main Content
Open an Account Apply for a Loan
Bank
CheckingOnline ServicesTransfers/PaymentsSavings RatesYouthDebit Card Round Up
Borrow
Vehicle LoansPersonal LoansCredit CardsMortgage LoansPayday Assistance LoanBusiness LoansLoan RatesPayment Calculators
Save
SavingsShare/IRA CDMoney MarketSavings RatesFinancial CalculatorsWealth Management
Service
InsuranceCard AlertsSavvy MoneyOnline Security CenterFinancial
ManagementGap and WarrantyCollateral ProtectionVisa Gift CardsHurricane Preparedness
Why Us?
Our StoryAll In 2 Finances ChallengeCommunity InvolvementYouth Council$100,000 GrantSponsorships &
DonationsScholarship ProgramAnnual ReportOpen an Account
Privacy Policy
Information We Disclose
We may disclose all of the information we collect as described above to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. We may also disclose information about you under other circumstances as permitted by law.
View our Privacy Notice
California Consumer Privacy Act
Safeguarding Member Information
Only employees who need information to provide products or services to you are allowed access to nonpublic information about you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with Federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.
At All In Federal Credit Union (All In CU), it is our policy to never request account information via email. If you receive an email from someone claiming to be affiliated with All In CU asking for personal information please contact us immediately at 334.598.4411 or 800.448.4096 or email our Fraud Department at allincu.fraud@allincu.com.
Credit Union members and the public may receive copies of this notice of privacy practices by contacting the Credit Union.
This notice meets the notification requirements of the National Credit Union Administration regulation on privacy of consumer information, Part 716.
Children’s Privacy Policy
We do NOT collect any personal information from a child without parental consent or parental notification. The Credit Union will not request that children submit personal information online nor will the Credit Union make personal information publicly available. The Credit Union does not allow anyone to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information. We do not entice any child with a special game, prize or other activity, to get them to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity. We are not responsible, however, for the practices of any third party sites to which we may provide links from within our site. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of all linked websites to become acquainted with their specific privacy practices.
Online Privacy
As a general policy, we do not automatically collect personal information from our website users. You may visit our website without having to provide any information about yourself. We do collect and store information on the domain used to access our website, the internet address of the website from which a user links to our website and the date and time of the visit. This information is used only to measure the number of visitors to our website and the route a user travels while within the Credit Union's website to better serve users in improved design and site navigation.
Cookies
Our website may use cookies (small pieces of information sent by our web server to a visitor's web browser that reminds our site about the user visits). We do not store confidential or sensitive information in cookies. The use of cookies allows us to enhance your Online Banking session and ease navigation through our website. For Online Banking, cookies are required to help protect the privacy of your transactions by, for example, automatically terminating the online session if you forget to log out. It is important to know that cookies cannot be used to capture your email address, obtain data from your hard drive or gain confidential or sensitive information about you (name, member number, SSN, etc.).
A cookie also lets us know if you are logging into your Online Banking from a computer or mobile device you normally use. For your protection, if you try to log in from a different computer or mobile device, you will be required to receive and input a new one-time passcode to confirm your identity.
You have the option to set your browser to notify you before accepting a cookie, allowing you to control whether a cookie is accepted or rejected. Information on these settings can be found under the "Help" menu in most browsers.
Third Party Link Disclaimer
Links to other web sites are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the All In CU web site.
Please Note:
All In Credit Union is not responsible for the availability or content of the third party site.
All In Credit Union does not represent either the third party site or the member, should the two enter into a transaction.
The privacy and security policies of the third party site may differ from those practiced by All In Credit Union.
An important Transaction Reminder about Regulation D
Certain accounts at all financial institutions are affected by the Federal Reserve Board’s Regulation D. At All In Federal Credit Union, these accounts are the Savings Accounts, Money Market Accounts and Christmas Club Accounts. (Transactions from All In Credit Union Checking Accounts are NOT limited by this regulation. The limitation does not apply to in-person transfers, ATM transfers or pre-authorized payments to a loan at the same Credit Union. Pursuant to Regulation D, electronic transfers from these Saving Accounts are limited to no more than six per calendar month. This includes transfers caused by overdrafts on your account. If you exceed these limitations, even though there is money in your Savings Account, the transfer will not take place. This can result in fees being imposed and exceeding these Regulation D limitations may cause your account to be closed. Learn More about Regulation D.
